Subtitles by JeeJa @AvistaZ
People here have believed in god since ancient times.
Maybe even before the existence of religion.
But for people of the Northeast
The definition of God,
May be different from others.
Every supernatural occurrence,
We call God.
Not just the spirits of the dead.
We believe that everything in
this world has a spirit.
Home
Forest, mountain
Tree
Field
Everything has a spirit.
In 2018, a documentary team traveled to Thailand to cover the lives of shamans.
After interviewing several shamans, the team decided to follow Nim’s daily life.
Bayan Spirit Medium
There are different types of "gods"
in the Northeast.
For example, god of healing, god of wealth,
god of ancestors, god of family.
Butterfly god, city god, god who eats offerings etc.
There are various types of gods.
Good spirits
will protect us,
bad spirits will bring pain and calamity.
Who is the spirit in your body?
I'll try to explain.
People call him "Martian"
At least people in the northeast call him that.
I am the shaman possessed by the spirit of Bayan.
Bayan is an ancestral god.
He is a good spirit who hass
blessed the people here.
Actually no one knows who he is
and where he came from.
But everyone believes in him
since ancient times.
"The Descendants of the Shamans" is a documentary.
My family,
for generations, they have been a medium for
the spirit of Bayan.
Since birth, my grandmother has been
possessed by the spirit of bayan.
Bayan only possesses women as a medium.
Many people came to my grandmother.
And every year there is a great ceremony.
In the past people will ask for fortune telling.
When grandmother died,
Her spirit was passed on to my aunt.
After my aunt,
It seemed to be attracted to my sister Noy,
But Noy refused the spirit.
Therefore, Bayan chose my body.
When a shaman is in trance, will the whole
body tremble and the voice will change?
You watch too much TV,
it's not really like this.
People come to me every day.
They come for treatment.
Some may even ask for a blessing.
Some also make offerings such
as alcohol and chicken.
Why did you come here?
He caught a snake and
soaked it in alcohol to drink.
-I told him not to drink it.
-After drinking his hands and feet got numb.
Where did you catch the snake?
In the cemetery.
I guess that's the reason why you're sick.
Because you ate the spirit of a beast.
Can you cure any disease?
If you have cancer,
come to me
Then you will die.
I can only cure disease
caused by the supernatural.
If you're possessed by an evil spirit or a
spirit from another realm, I can heal it.
But if it's a common disease,
go to a doctor.
I never wanted to be a shaman.
At the time, what did you do?
I'm very sick and can't be cured.
I was so desperate, I wanted to kill myself.
Because I was chosen, I ran away.
Although, in the end I accepted it.
And that's amazing.
My daily life is just praying
and doing rituals.
People come to me, to ask for help.
Some of them are in terrible condition.
Anyway, I'm happy now.
In fact, I can't remember why I use to refuse,
And why I was angry with him.
THE MEDIUM (RANG ZONG)
We're going to Willow's funeral,
can you tell me who he was?
Willow is the husband of my sister Noy.
Last year he found out that he had cancer.
Condolences.
I don't know why members of the Asatia family,
die tragically.
His grandfather was killed by his men.
When his father's factory went bankrupt,
his father burned it down, in order to receive
insurance compensation.
After being caught,
he committed suicide by drinking poison.
As for his eldest son Mike.
He died in a motorcycle accident
last year.
Hmm...
Are you alright?
I almost forgot how you look.
Does someone have to die,
so we can meet?
-Do you want me to bring this to them?
-Yes, please bring it.
-I forgot all the faces of my family.
-Alright, I'll take it.
He's the priest of the church,
Noy frequents.
Thank you for coming.
Min, find a chair for the priest.
Min, are you okay?
I heard you were the first,
to see your father's body.
I'm fine.
There are three of us in my family.
Manit is the eldest brother.
Stop smoking, it'll get you killed.
Would you like a glass of water?
Noy is the second sister and then there's me.
And also,
Noy's husband, Willow, who just passed away.
Not long ago, Noy's son Mike also died.
Now...
Noy lives with
her only child, Min.
Actually Noy and Willow got married late.
After they got married,
Noy inherited her mother-in-law's
dog meat shop.
Previously, it was her mother-in-law
who ran it.
I don't know why she took it.
The government prohibits selling dog meat,
but they still sell it secretly.
These two don't get along,
I didn't know what the problem is,
but it's been going on for a long time.
I also tried to mend their relationship.
-Put on your own shoes.
-Don't wear other people's shoes.
Thank you.
Aunt.
Mom asked you to go home
to get something for me.
I've written everything down here.
Aunt Nimes.
-There you are.
-Is the door closed?
-Yes
-Lucky can't leave the house.
-Stop it.
You brought the wrong clothes,
it should be the thicker one.
Then you go and
get it yourself.
Uncle, what did you say earlier?
Did I say something?
-Damn it, say it one more time.
-What did I say?
Just because of the card, why are you cursing me?
I didn't say anything.
What are you doing?
What did i do?
What? You said I look like a prostitute.
Min, stop!
I didn't say that.
Mom, do something.
Min, stop it!
-Come out first.
-No, he did say it.
-Who said something?
-You bastard.
-Calm down.
-Let go of me, mom.
-Min, calm down.
He did say it earlier.
I didn't say anything.
Does Min usually drink this much?
She did drink but I didn't know,
she drank that much.
It's the first time,
I've seen her like that.
-Fine, go.
-I'll go first.
Drive carefully.
Min?
Who died?
The blind grandma who lives back there.
How did she die?
I don't know.
Min.
Nim, what's wrong?
Why did you go into Min's room?
What are you looking for?
I'm asking you, why won't you answer?
Why are you suddenly like this.
I'll help you find it, but you need to
tell me what's going on...
Look, you see this?
You know what this is?
What...
What are you doing in my room,
everyone out!
-Min, wait a minute.
-Mom, you too.
Min, did you have a bad dream
or hear a strange sound?
-Nothing, I said nothing.
-Min.
I told you to get out!
What are you recording?
Do you know what this is made of?
Tell me, does Min show any strange behaviour?
Noy.
I can take care of my child, leave.
What's that thing in Min's closet?
It's called "Wampa Taba".
It's believed to ward off evil spirits.
Entering people's room and rummage
through things without permission.
So annyoing,
right?
Why did you put "Wampa Taba" in you room?
I'm not a child, I'm an adult.
Why did you stare at the blind grandma,
at the funeral yesterday?
What blind grandma?
Do you see anyone there?
Yes, I can see them.
What's the matter?
When the Documentary Team reviewed
the video footage,
Min's strange behavior
was caught on camera.
Is there any explanation for
Min's strange behaviour?
From what I've seen so far,
there are several reasons why.
Is it a sign that the spirit of Bayan
is going to possess her?
I don't know.
If it's true that the spirit of Bayan is passed down from
generation to generation, this is an opportunity.
It is rare for a documentary team to record the
occurrence of a Bayan's medium transfer.
Finally the Documentary Team decided
to cover Min and her family.
Sir, do you want to keep recording all day?
It's okay. Just take it easy.
Can you talk about your work?
Sure.
Human Resources Office
I work in human resources.
I'm responsible to help
people find work.
Number Six.
Hello.
I woke up at 5am.
After waking up, I have breakfast and
arrive at the office around 7-8am.
There aren't many visitors in the afternoon,
so I can rest for a while.
Actually, this job
it's not too difficult.
Do you like your job?
Yes, I like it. I love being able
to help others find a job.
Really?
Of course, is this an interview
for Miss Thailand?
What do you think of your aunt being a shaman?
Witch doctor?
To be honest,
I think it's all fake.
Suddenly dancing like a monkey
and calling for god...
What exactly are you doing.
I've also met someone who said
she was a Doraemon shaman.
Very funny.
What is a Doraemon shaman like?
Maybe when in trance, you will make sounds like
"Ang Ang Ang"
You want me to cast a shaman spell?
See?
Anyone can do it, you can just learn it
from watching a video.
-How much is it?
-100 baht.
Thank you.
I don't know why it's banned.
People here, have been eating dog meat
for a long time.
Still, you're selling dog meat and
keep a dog at home.
Don't you think it's weird?
Not at all.
Don't people who raise goldfish or koi,
also eat fish?
May I ask you about the Bayan spirit?
Can you remember what it feelt like,
when Bayan was about to possess you?
I was probably 20 years
old at the time.
My body feels weird, people say it's a divine disease.
And my head hurts a lot too.
Every day I have my menstrual period
and it lasts for 5 months.
Since my aunt is also a shaman,
she said I should inherit it.
But I don't want to be a shaman.
So I embraced christianity.
I pray to God not to become a shaman.
Forgive, as you will be forgiven.
To those who have trespassed against us.
If the trespass is unforgivable, so be it.
Then something strange happened
to my sister Nim.
At that time she learned how to sew in the city.
She suddenly fainted and lost consciousness.
No specific cause.
We were terrified at the time
and took Nimes home.
Not long after, the spirit of
Bayan possessed Nim.
No one knows why.
I feel guilty when I think about it.
Nim became a shaman instead of me.
What should you do if Bayan possessed you?
If you ask stupid things like this
in an interview.
It's best not to have the interview
and record it.
Wow, you look beautiful Min.
But, why are you wearing other people's shoes?
I must look beautiful on the day of celebration.
Does it feel comfortable to wear?
Not bad but it feels a bit big.
Has Min's behaviour been
different lately?
What's different is not only her behaviour.
I don't know what's wrong with her.
But she looks like a
different person.
Wait a moment...
Hey! Min, where are you going?
Stop! That's a kids game.
I'll get in trouble.
But, I want to play.
Are you crazy, hurry up and
get out.
Min, you idiot!
What are you doing Min?
Idiot.
What are you doing?
Lisa!
Stop recording.
I'm not feeling right now.
I said stop recording.
Human Resources Office
Min, why did you leave me with this idiot.
Don't ask for my help again, bitch.
You hear? Min!
Wait a minute, I'm coming.
Hey Min, why are you sleeping here?
Get up. Take a shower
and get ready for work.
Min. Min.
What's wrong, Min?
Where did you sleep last night?
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
Stop going to nightclubs.
Min, what is wrong?
Nothing, just my regular period.
Since when? Talk to me for a minute.
Min, talk to me. How long have you had your period?
-Pang, have you seen Manit?
-He went to meet his friend.
-Who?
-I don't know either.
Manit, what are you doing here?
What will you say to your wife and kid?
Come with me, I have something to tell you.
Hurry up!
Don't you think Min's condition,
is similar to Nim's back then?
Right.
-Leave it to Nim, she'll help her.
-I don't want my daughter to be a shaman.
What if Bayan will still possess Min?
What would you do?
-I really don't know.
-Think carefully.
What are you looking at?
Honey, calm down.
-Don't meddle in my business!
-Hey, what are you doing?
-What are you doing?
-Drive the bus.
-Get off, get out of the bus.
-No.
-Sir, stop the bus.
-Why do I have to get out?
-Are you crazy?
-You're crazy! Bitch.
Bastard!
-Go to hell.
-You bastards!
Curse you!
Damn it.
What's wrong with me, you idiot.
What are you saying?
Leave, all of you!
Fuck all of you!
-Are these all the recordings?
-Yes.
Is Min acting weird
and look like somebody else?
She use to act like a child.
Is there any other behavior besides that?
Just that, nothing else.
-Did you see my bracelet?
-What?
I think I lost it while picking up things,
at my brother-in-law's funeral.
-Which bracelet?
-My brown bracelet.
-The one you usually wear?
-Yes.
-The one you are wearing every day.
Where did you go that day?
I came to get medicine and a scarf in Noy's room.
In that case, you may have dropped it upstairs.
Go there to look for it.
If you can't find it. I'll help you look for it.
Look well.
-Min?
How are you?
Did a strange voice call for you?
Did you respond to it?
-*.
-Nim, what are you doing with Min?
Nothing. Just a greeting between aunt and niece.
What did she ask?
I told you there was nothing.
-You called Nim, right?
-What are you talking about.
She only came to find her
missing bracelet.
I'll just go.
Min, are you okay?
What did your aunt say?
What were you talking about?
Min, what's wrong?
Mom...
Tell me.
Mom, I don't want to be a shaman.
I won't let you become a shaman.
-Don't worry.
-Please help me.
-Mom will help you.
Why do you think Nim came to
look for Min?
You think I will let my daughter,
become a shaman?
Nim can't understand. Because
she doesn't have any children.
No matter what, I won't let my daughter
become a shaman.
Mrs. Gandalaya, please take your medicine at counter 2.
Mother will get it for you.
Wait here.
My head hurt so much, it felt like exploding.
My stomach and back
everything hurts.
My vagina hurts too.
It hurts so much that I can't pee.
Even doctors can't help me.
Have you had any strange dreams lately?
I've had the same dream almost every night.
There's a big man.
With a body full of inscriptions.
Wearing a traditional red vest and pants.
In my dream...
He holds a sword,
With both legs dangling,
His big tongue licked the tip of the sword.
And also...
Beneath him was a headless man,
covered in blood.
The head seemed to want
to say something to me.
What did he say?
I tried to hear what
he had to say,
But there was no sound.
-Min?
-Are you okay?
-Leave me alone.
This will end badly,
can you stand up?
-Come on, stand up.
-Leave!
We'd better go to the hospital.
I told you to leave me alone.
Hey, come with me for a second.
Stop recording.
You bastard, what are you saying?
You want to fire me?
Get lost!
Min?
-Did you take your medicine this morning?
-Min. Min.
-Are you okay?
-Min, change your clothes here.
I'll be waiting for you here.
Okay everything is done,
let's fix your hair.
Hey!
Min!
Your daughter is so pretty.
Your mother is here.
Min!
She didn't look over here.
Min.
Where are you going?
Going to work.
What are you doing here?
Get out!
Security, get her out!
I've been missing something at work.
So I went to check the CCTV to make sure.
You know what I saw?
Please see for yourself.
This woman is outrageous.
Min!
Min?
Are you taking a shower?
Min!
Noy!
Sweetie!
Oh my god, what's going on?
*!
Don't just stand there, help.
Noy, call an ambulance.
Hurry up and call an ambulance.
*
Are you alright?
Send an ambulance immediately!
Why are you here?
What are doing?
Nim, stop all this.
She would accept the spirit of bayan.
Can you do the inheritance ritual?
I don't want to see my daughter like this.
Min can't do the inheritance ritual.
What do you mean?
Because right now, it's not the spirit
of bayan in her body.
Not bayan? What do you mean?
Look at her symptoms,
haven't we experienced them before?
Wouldn't she be cured if she
accepted bayan and become a shaman?
Not like this.
Please, don't be like this.
Manit, come with me.
I'll be right back, just wait.
This is your niece. You have to help her.
Don't you feel sorry for her?
Open the door.
Are you sure you want to open it?
-Open the door.
-What are you going to do?
Open it!
Nothing will happen, right?
Have you told Min?
How did Mike die?
Doesn't everyone know,
that he died in a motorcycle accident?
I want to know the truth.
Now I know what the relationship
between the two of them is.
You know what happens to a soul
who commits suicide, right?
Don't you know?
Tell me where Mike killed himself.
The entire Documentary Team
is confident in Nim's prediction,
that something
else possessed Min.
Just slowly.
What will you do if Nim
refuses to perform the ritual?
Even if she refuses, I will find a way.
Although...
It is against my beliefs.
I have to do something.
Mike!
It's like a punishment to you, right?
I know you like Min but you can't take her.
Are you listening?
Noy, do you really want to do this?
Just drive the car.
-*.
-Okay.
Stop the ritual, I said stop!
Stop!
Nim!
-Stop it!
-What are you doing?
Do you know how dangerous this is,
what if another spirit will enter her body?
Then what should I do?
My daughter is dying.
-You don't care about her.
-What do you know?.
Why can't I help you?
-I have my way and I'll definitely help.
-What are you going to do?
-Even then, how can you let this person
do the ritual?
-Should I just let my daughter die?
Do you know this person?
When will you do it?
After my daugther died?
Min!
Min, stop it!
Stop it!
Nim, what about Min?
Where's Min?
-Where did Min go?
-Lie down, take a rest first.
Min.
What about Min?
My daugther Min.
Nim, how long has she been like this?
I have to find Min. Nim, you have to help me.
In order for Min to return,
we have to perform a ritual.
But first Noy has to accept the spirit of bayan.
We have to ask for forgiveness from bayan.
Even though Noy sinned by
rejecting the spirit of bayan.
But I believe that Bayan is a merciful god.
Put this on your head.
If she means it, God will forgive her.
Present the offerings.
-What's that smell?
-Take a look.
We have to collect the items Min collected.
Because we'll use it for the ritual.
What are these things?
There are traces of spirits on these things.
Min has been in contact with them.
The Evil Spirit sensed Mike's possessive
feelings, and used them to deceive Min.
Min has been in contact with them.
Nim look at this. God, why did she put it there?
The Evil Spirit sensed Mike's possessive
feelings, and used them to deceive Min.
Nim look at this. God, why did she put it there?
These are her baby shoes.
-Nim
-Yes?
Also look around the house,
everything has to be removed.
We have to perform the ritual where Mike killed himself.
I will pray for Min, that Mike doesn't hurt her.
I will let Mike know that Min loves him too.
I know Mike, you're angry and
want to take revenge against your family.
But I won't let anything happen to Min.
I don't know how long the ritual will last.
I might have to spend a few days and nights,
Until I know where Min went.
A taxi driver came with his dashboard camera
after he heard the news.
He picked up Min around 3am.
After getting in the car, the driver asked
where she was going, but she didn't answer.
Let's take a look at the video.
Ma'am,
Where are you going?
Ma'am?
Ma'am? Has she gone mad?
I'm leaving.
What is this.
Oh my god.
I don't know if the video is faulty or not.
Anyway, I've sent it to the forensic team.
But I don't think
we can find her either.
If there's any news, we'll let you know.
I am worried about my daughter's condition.
I don't know if she's still alive.
*
I can only pray,
to God or Buddha.
To return my daughter.
I've been everywhere.
The house of her friend, ex-boyfriend, all of them.
But no one saw her.
I've used all the ways
for chanting and praying.
If praying would solve everything,
I would have done it a long time ago.
Dog Meat Shop
Temporarily closed for repair
Eever since Min disappeared, my family's
situation has gotten worse.
One of them is Noy,
she doesn't eat and sleep.
It's been a month, but you
still haven't found a clue?
You just sit here and eat the tax dollars we pay.
-It's not like that, sir.
-You're all the same!
It's been a month...
And you just sit here quietly.
We've been looking for clues.
-What are you guys doing here?
-Everyone's working.
Then why are you just sitting
here like an idiot.
All I see is that you're all
just sitting here.
No clues,
No news,
at all.
I was fooled by their trick.
Actually this has nothing
to do with Mike.
Then who kidnapped Min?
Yasantia Spinning Factory
Min?
Min, wake up!
Her fever has gone down.
But there are symptoms of dehydration and malnutrition.
And some minor bruises and abrasions.
Will she be okay?
We'll check her again
after she regains consciousness.
Now everything is clear.
At least Min wasn't badly injured.
I will go to the mountains again.
To pray and make offerings to Bayan.
God, Who would do such a thing?
Where have you been all this time?
At least eat a little.
Food won't even go into her mouth.
Currently Min is possessed
by an unknown spirit.
Who are you?
I ask. who are you really?
I am Bayan.
I will ask you again, who are you?
Guess, who I really am.
Guess...
Min, don't do this.
Have you gone mad? Why would
you do this?
Why is she like this?
You like vaginas, don't you?
You really like it.
Min, don't do this.
Stop it, Min!
-Hold her.
-Let me go.
-Grab her.
-Take it off.
-Hold her properly!
Grab her, quick!
Dip her finger in the glass.
Do you know,
why you're a shaman?
It's all because of your dear sister.
She wears her best clothes
for your every day.
She even put a talisman in your shoe.
She does everything
for you, to replace her as a shaman.
Did you know that?
Find something to tie her up, quick.
Hurry up.
Hurry up. Once you're done,
go outside.
Don't record it before going out.
Go!
I need someone's help.
Nim, about what Min said earlier.
Please forgive me.
Don't worry. No matter what happens,
I will save my niece.
Santi, you're still doing this
embarrassing ritual, apparently.
I also have to live.
Min, wait a moment...
She's possessed by a strange spirit, right?
Her condition now,
is like a car that's out of control.
-Who exactly possessed her?
-She's not alone.
I don't know who they are.
It's too many to count.
I can only feel their presence.
Evil spirit with all kinds of resentment.
They collect all the evil spirits
and even the unfortunate souls
which turned into a beast spirit.
From the Dog Spirit,
Centipede,
Spider,
To the spirit of nautre.
A powerful evil spirit,
that fuses all spirits together.
This is where Min was found.
The exorcism must be performed here.
All the evil spirits gathered here for Min.
When the Evil Spirit is removed, so will
the Evil Spirit in Min's body.
Why did it choose Min?
Have you heard of your husband's ancestors?
How many people were killed by Willow's ancestors.
A dying man cursed this family.
The curse is passed down from generation to generation.
That's why Willow married you.
The one who rejected Bayan.
After that,
Everything has been decided.
One must be sacrificed to do penance.
And that person is Min.
Do you believe?
That all of this is fate.
You don't have to worry,
the day of the exorcism will soon be determined.
Who decides?
God?
Buddha?
Which one?
Why should my daughter pay,
for the karma accumulated by my ancestor?
Why can't it be just me?
Sit down for a while.
Don't think too much.
Min will recover once her exorcism is complete.
Bayan will help us.
When I was sick, people said that Bayan wanted to possess me.
But I felt nothing, except pain.
May I ask you?
Have you met the spirit of Bayan?
Do you believe Bayan is real?
-Of course.
-Have you seen him with your own eyes?
-Not yet.
-How can you believe in it?
I can only feel it. I feel his presence.
If we believe, Bayan will help us.
Prepare yourself for the ritual.
This evil spirit is very strong,
we must be prepared.
We also need a lot of amulets and spells.
In order to maximize my strength, I have to
extert it on a wooden stick.
Just in case I prepared a lot of alcohol and incense.
And he most important thing is that I have to do this ritual with Nim.
We must unite. Even though,
it's difficult we have to try.
I've been doing this for a long time,
but this ritual is still challenging.
I want to see how strong the evil spirit is.
She doesn't even want to eat right now.
I tried to talk to her but
she did not respond.
I am so worried.
Nim didn't stop by because she's
busy preparing for the exorcism.
Every morning things
in the house are scattered.
And I think Min did it.
I know that it is Min who does this
every night but why.
The documentary team installed
cameras at the house,
to find out what Min
is doing every night.
6 Days before the exorcism.
What's up Lucky?
5 Days before the exorcism.
4 Days before the exorcism.
3 Days before the exorcism
If that's the case, stop recording.
-Sir, please.
-Stop it, all of you just leave.
Please wait until it's finished.
-Look a little more.
-What is goig on?
Why her?
If things are like this,
shouldn't we just leave.
If you want to leave, please.
I will stay with with my daughter.
Honestly, I was afraid to watch it.
But she is still my daughter.
Nim, will help her to recover.
Nim, is well known, she's
helped a lot of people.
She can definitely save Min, right?
After seeing Min's behavior, her family
agreed to put in an extra camera.
Why does my stomache hurt?
2 Days before the exorcism.
Finished. Now she can't get in.
Not even through our dreams.
Alright, let's grab
something to eat.
- Min!
- Hey, Get up!
Disgusting.
Pon!
Where's Pon!?
-What's wrong?
-Min took my son.
-Hah?
-Where did she take him?
-Hurry up, find her!
-Min took my son.
-Where did Min take him?
Quick, find her!
Why is Min doing this,
quickly find her!
You're crazy, why did you take my son!
-Have you seen Min?
-I didn't see her.
Min, damn you.
Min, where are you?
-Pon!
-Don't worry mother is here.
Min, wake up!
Min, Min? Let him go.
1 Day before the exorcism.
Nim!
-Is something wrong?
-Why aren't you returning my calls?
I heard a voice, but no one answered.
-Is anyone there?
-Yes.
Nim!
-Nim!
-Are you there?
What's this?
Nim! Nim!
Nim, wake up!
You over there, help her.
Nim died while sleeping.
Doctors to not know the cause of death.
Because of me, Nim is dead.
Eveyrthing that happend to Min,
it's my fault.
I have nobody else.
All I can do now is protect my daughter.
I'm willing to die for her.
Why did Nim die? She must
have been killed by the evil spirit, right?
We can't do anything.
What did you say?
What do you mean?
Master, what are we going to do?
Don't worry. The ritual will
be carried out tomorrow.Just
follow my orders.
Day of the exorcism.
-Here?
-Yes, just put it there.
Guru Santi, can you explain the procedure of
the ritual today?
I will hold the ritual on the 5th floor.
By inviting the evil spirit in Min's body.
I will lure them out.
Then I will put the spirit in a jar.
After the spirit is sealed,
I will bury the jar in a secluded place.
And bury everything related to the spirit.
Based on what happened to Nim,
Isn't it to dangerous to perform the ritual?
Right.
But you've seen what's on the back of Manit's car?
There's a sticker that says "this car is red".
This car is red
What does it have to do with the ritual?
No one should leave this place
until the ritual is over.
Come!
Who's knocking?
I dont' know.
Noy!
-Noy
-Are you okay?
-She passed out.
-Let's rest for a while.
Noy!
Noy, are you alright?
Can you hear me?
Is anyone there?
Why did you lock me up?
Mom, are you outside? Please open the door.
Has the spirit gone?
Who knows.
-Aunt.
-Min?
Please open the door.
Min, are you okay?
Open the door.
Are you quiet?
Aunt, I beg you, please open the door.
I don't know.
The guru said that not to open the door,
until the ritual is over.
-Open the door for me.
-Min.
Aunt, I'm locked up, please open the door.
-Wait a minute.
-Mom, please open the door.
They haven't contacted me.
Bi, where did everyone go?
Please open the door
Min, are you okay?
Open the door, my son inside.
-No.
-Open the door.
-I said my son is inside.
-Don't.
My son is inside.
What are you talking about?
He's still in his bed.
He's in there, can't you hear him?
-My son is inside.
-The Guru said, the door must not be opened.
-Please, check again.
-Min, please return Pon.
Open the door.
-I told you, I can't.
-Open the door.
No, please check again.
Open the door.
-Look at the bed again.
-Oh.
-Hah?
-Open the door.
Ma'am,
you can't!
Ma'am, wake up!
Pon! Pon!
Master, what's wrong?
Master.
Master!
What happened?
Master, what's wrong with you?
Master!
Min, where is my son?
Damn, open the door. Please open the door!
Help me!
Help!
The door won't open.
No!
What happend?
Why is the light off?
Turn on the camera light.
Damn, where did everyone go?
Hello, what happened?
Where did everyone gone?
Sir?
Let's just go.
I can't see anything.
Oh shit.
Oh lord.
Sweetie!
Noy!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I can feel it.
The spirit of Bayan is with us.
Bayan is with me.
Bayan watched me.
The ritual must continue.
Collect the broken jar.
We have to lock up the evil spirit again.
Find it, quickly.
Get the incense.
Do you want me to record you?
Why is the incense upside down?
Don't
Uncle, uncle!
No!
Evil spirit!
Get out of my daughter's body!
By the power of Bayan, you shall be crushed.
Is it you, Min?
Give me back my daughter.
Give her back!
I said give her back!
Min do you hear mom's voice?
Are you still there?
Don't be like this, to mother.
Min are you listening?
Min, mother was guilty.
Mother was wrong.
Come back.
Oh god, please save Min.
Please save my daughter.
Min don't give up.
Min, don't, don't do this to mom.
Yasantia
Nim's last interview.
What happened at the altar earlier?
I'm afraid the exorcism ritual,
won't work.
So what? Haven't the preperations
been completed?
Maybe it's all useless.
What does it mean?
To be honest,
I don't know either.
I was never sure,
that Bayan really existed in my body.
You mean?
I don't know either.